- It was?
- Oh, yeah, going slow really worked.
(Leonard:)You're kidding.
(Leonard:)Never worked for me.
(Stuart:)Yeah, last night at dinner
I did what you told me.
(Stuart:)I went really slow, I kept my distance...
(Stuart:)...and two bottles of wine later,
we were making out.
(Leonard:)Wine? I didn't say to give her wine.
(Stuart:)It doesn't matter.
That's where it all went to hell.
(Leonard:)During the kissing?
(Leonard:)What did you do, sneeze in her mouth?
I did that to a girl once.
(Stuart:)No, everything was good and really hot.
And I said, "Oh, Penny"...
(Stuart:)...and right where she was supposed
to say, "Oh, Stuart" she said...
(Stuart:)...your name.
- Leonard?
- That is your name, right?
Yeah. No, yeah, it is.
(Leonard:)Wow, I'm sorry.
(Leonard:)That must've been the last thing
you wanted to hear.
(Stuart:)Well, it beats,
"You know I'm a dude, right?"